globaladspace.com 2018-08-31

# Globaladspace | Ad Network | Privacy Policy

#### Introduction

Global Ad Space is The Global Audience Platform enabling advertisers and marketers across the world to communicate with their audiences and helping publishers to grow their revenues with better optimization and campaign planning. We are headquartered in US, with an office in Washington, USA. We provide this privacy policy so that we may inform you about how our ad optimization technology, including our Ad Network Platform for online advertisers including Real-Time Bidding Service (collectively, the “Service”) gathers and processes information on behalf of (i) advertisers, agencies and ad networks, and any other media-buying clients (collectively “Demand Partners”); and (ii) website owners, mobile application owners, ad networks, ad exchanges, sell-side platforms and any other suppliers of advertising inventory for sale (collectively “Supply Partners”); wherein Demand Partners and Supply Partners in (i) and (ii) above together are “Clients”. 

Global Ad Space recognizes and values your privacy and we are committed to protecting the confidentiality of your personal information. In order to better protect you, we have adopted a strong privacy policy that allows you to monitor the information you have provided us. We will seek your consent before collecting any information about you, and you will always be aware of exactly what we are going to use the information for. If at any time you wish to withdraw your personal information, all you are required to do is to contact us and tell us exactly what information you would like removed. 

You will find an explanation of our Privacy Policy below; to give you a better understanding of the lengths we would go to protect you. 

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, so please visit globaladspace.com regularly to review our privacy statement.

#### Collection and use of Information on this Website

Personally Identifiable Information. This Website is directed to our Clients and prospective Clients, who are businesses. The Website is not directed to consumers. We may collect Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") via this Website when a visitor voluntarily provides it to us. PII means 

Name  
Postal address  
Email address  
Telephone Number

Any other information collected from you

We do not sell, trade, permit usage or rent your personal information to any third party unless we have been expressly authorized by you either in writing or electronically to do so. We may at times provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties; however this information when disclosed will be in an aggregate form and does not contain any of your personally identifiable information. We conduct internal audits to ensure that we are complying with the policies in place to protect you. We may use that information to respond to your requests and inquiries and for other purposes. 

We may disclose your personal information solely in the legitimate conduct of business to deliver services and to provide special offers designed to meet your demands. We may also release information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with legal or regulatory requirements; (2) enforce or apply terms of the our Web site user agreement; or (3) protect our rights, property or safety of the rights of others.   
We expressly forbid our clients from sending us any of your personal information. To the best of our ability, we have taken all the precautions possible to avoid receiving personal information from our clients. If, despite these measures, we do receive some personal information from a client, we shall take all measures to remove such personal information from our servers and records.

#### Use of Cookie

“Cookies” are strings of text that a web site transmits to a user's computer. Cookies enable a website to keep track of a user's preferences and activities relating to that website. Our website creates a temporary cookie for each visit in order to facilitate the visit. These cookies automatically expire as soon as you leave our website. If you do not wish to receive these cookies, you may set your browser to reject the cookies, although doing so may affect your ability to perform certain transactions on our website. 

The main purpose of using these cookies is to improve your experience. For example, our cookies allow you to login without repeatedly typing the registered email address or registration number and password. We also use them to deliver information and fresh content specific to your interests. Cookies are widely used on most major sites. Cookies can also be used to track a user’s browsing or online purchasing habits and to target advertisements to specific users. 

Updating / Deleting your PII If you'd like us to update, correct, or delete any PII that you have provided to us on this Website, please send your request to us and we will process your request.

#### REPORTS

Globaladspace.com shall have the sole responsibility for calculation of statistics, including impressions and revenues generated through Publisher's inventory. Statistics shall be available to Publisher online by accessing to the URL to be provided by Globaladspace.com. Publisher understands that Globaladspace.com online statistics may not be 100% accurate at the moment; therefore the Globaladspace.com may make adjustments to Publisher's online statistics (i.e. statistical errors) at the end of each calendar month.

#### Security of Personal Information

At Global Ad Space we make protection of your personal information from loss, theft or misuse our top priority. All information we have collected is stored using the same security measures that we use to protect our own proprietary corporate data. Only authorized users are able to access the data we collect and store. 

At times we may collect Non-Personal Information (NPI) via our service, including but not limited to your IP host address, the date, time, and time zone of the ad request, pages viewed, browser type, the referring URL, and your computer’s operating system. We retain this NPI at a user level for a certain period in order to ensure that our service is functioning properly. We may also retain data at an aggregated level – so that no individual user, albeit anonymous, could be picked out from the data – indefinitely for purposes of reporting and system analytics.

#### Other Sites

Global Ad Space is only responsible for the privacy statement and content of this website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the use of cookies on websites that you may have accessed from this site.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

In the future, we may need to change this privacy policy. All changes will be made here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

#### Your Consent to this Privacy Policy

By submitting your information, you consent to the use of that information as set out in this Privacy Policy. We welcome your views on this website and the Privacy Policy. If you have questions or comments about our administration of your personal information, please contact us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

Accept Close
